Guide to Speeches in the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. John Brademas) RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception honoring Dean West, Graduate School of Business Administration, NYU, 3 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 34)
  - Speech before the National Council for Children & Television (NY), 5 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 35)
  - Spain Talking Points, Spain, 6 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 36)
  - Italy Talking Points, Italy, 6 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 37)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Sir Steven Runciman, NYU, 18 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 38)
  - Remarks delivered at a convocation honoring Sir Steven Runciman, NYU, 18 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 39)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Robert K. Massie (NY), 19 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 40)
  - Remarks delivered at the inauguration of President Jerry Lee, Gallaudet College, (Washington, D.C.), 19 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 41)
  - Bowsher Lecture, NYU, 22 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 42)
  - Presentation of Nathan S. Kline Medal of Merit to Rosalynn Carter, NYU, 22 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 43)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a press conference for the School of Continuing Education, NYU, 23 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 44)
  - Brief remarks at the opening of the 26th Street Dormitory, NYU, 24 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 45)
  - Brief remarks by Mr. Tisch at the opening of the 26th Street Dormitory, NYU, 24 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 46)
  - "Election '84: Implications for Education," Wright State University (OH), 25 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 47)
  - Brief remarks at a dinner honoring Marie Schwartz, NYU, 29 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 48)
  - "Resolved that Education is a Federal Concern: A Congressman's View," Gannon Seminar (NY), 30 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 49)
  - "Education on the National Agenda: Perspectives & Prospects," Gannon Lecture (NY), 31 October 1984 (Box 617, Folder 50)
  - Brief remarks at the Japan Center Conference Lunch, NYU, 2 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 51)
  - Campaign Gala, NYU, 3 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 52)
  - Parents' Day, NYU, 4 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 53)
  - "Engaging a Whole World: The Humanities in the 1980s," convocation at Fairfield University (CT), 8 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 55)
  - Remarks delivered at the dedication of the Rusk Institute, NYU, 9 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 56)
  - Talking points for a dinner honoring Eppie Lederer (NY), 10 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 57)
  - Remarks delivered at Charles Haskins Dinner, School of Business and Public Administration, NYU, 12 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 58)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a reception in Rubin, NYU, 12 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 59)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Sir Ronald Syme, NYU, 14 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Convocation, NYU, 14 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 61)
  - Remarks delivered before the American Council of Life Insurance (Boston, MA), 14 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 62)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, 15 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 63)
  - Chet Huntley Lecture (speaker: Henry Grunewald), NYU, 15 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 64)
  - "The Elections are Over: What Next," lecture delivered at the School of Law Alumni Day, NYU, 17 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 65)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a cocktail reception at the Spanish Institute, NYU, 17 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 66)
  - Presentation of an award to Mr. Koch, School of Continuing Education 50th Birthday Party, NYU, 19 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 67)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a Faculty Resources Network luncheon, NYU, 20 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 68)
  - Brief remarks preceding a lecture by Angelos Angelopoulos, NYU, 20 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 69)
  - Presentation of a Doctorate of Humane Letters to Archbishop Iakovos, NYU, 25 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 70)
  - "The American Administration After the Elections," delivered at the Atlantic Institute for International Affairs (Paris), 29 November 1984 (Box 617, Folder 71)
  - Introductory remarks at the Banco de la Provincia de Buenos Aires Seminar, NYU, 3 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 72)
  - Brief remarks at the dedication of the Nichols Center, NYU, 4 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 73)
  - Second Bobst Awards Dinner, NYU, 4 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 74)
  - Presentation of award, Long I Grotto Luncheon (NY), 4 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 75)
  - Remarks on receiving a Humanitarian Award from the Hellenic Medical Society of NY (NY), 8 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 76)
  - Metro Center Benefit Lunch, NYU, 10 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 78)
  - "The Place of Faith in Public Life: A Personal Perspective," Liss Lecture, University of Notre Dame (IN), 11 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 79)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Harry and Lucy Moses, NYU, 13 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 80)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the Brittany Hall Façade Project, NYU, 13 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 81)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Filomen Greenberg, NYU, 17 December 1984 (Box 617, Folder 82)
  - Business International Chief Executive Officers Roundtable (Jamaica), 6 January 1985 (Box 617, Folder 83)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Norman Lear, 8 January 1985 (Box 617, Folder 85)
  - National Retail Merchants Annual Convention (NY), 14 January 1985 (Box 617, Folder 86)
  - Introductory remarks at a CBS/NYU seminar on manuscripts (NY), 29 January 1985 (Box 617, Folder 87)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Association of American Colleges (Washington, D.C.), 10 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 88)
  - "Teaching Experiences: Beware of Editors Bearing Myths," editorial in Barron's, 1 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 89)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Frank Spencer, NYU, 12 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 90)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Alan Landsburg, NYU, 19 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 91)
  - Remarks delivered at the Brittany Residence Hall Open House, NYU, 21 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 92)
  - Testimony Before Committee on Education & Labor (Washington, D.C.), 27 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 93)
  - Metropolitan Life Reception (NY), 25 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 94)
  - Annual Management Meeting of Cooper Industries (Houston, TX), 28 February 1985 (Box 617, Folder 95)
  - Winter Celebration, NYU, 2 March 1985 (Box 617, Folder 96)
  - Law School UN Conference, NYU, 1-2 March 1985 (Box 617, Folder 97)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at dinner honoring Ephraim Urback, NYU, 5 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254659
  - David Kriser Dinner, NYU, 7 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 2)
  - Orientation for prospective students, NYU, 9 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 3)
  - Remarks on receiving the Charles Evans Hughs Gold Medal from the National Conference of Christians & Jews (NY), 11 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 4)
  - Testimony before Budget Committee (Washington, D.C.), 12 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 5)
  - NYU Day in Albany, 13 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 6)
  - "Education: The Quest for Quality" (Elkhart, IN), 20 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Institute Awards Dinner, NYU, 20 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 8)
  - Remarks delivered at the Raul Alfonsin Convocation, NYU, 21 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 9)
  - EACUBO Speech (NY), 22 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 10)
  - Opening remarks delivered at the Sir David Hunt Seminar, NYU, 25 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 11)
  - Edward Bernays Presidential Citation Ceremony, NYU, 26 March 1985 (Box 618, Folder 12)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Dean Richard West, NYU, 4 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 14)
  - Mary Lasker Testimonial (NY), 5 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 15)
  - Dinner for New Trustees, NYU, 9 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 16)
  - Introduction of Mayor Koch at an event honoring Trustees' Scholars, NYU, 10 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 17)
  - Senate Remarks, NYU, 11 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 18)
  - Introduction of Jack Kemp at Graduate School of Business Administration Alumni Day, NYU, 13 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 19)
  - New York Times Editorial Lunch, New York, Apr 15, 1985 (Box 618, Folder 20)
  - Adelphi University Convocation (Long Island, NY), 17 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 21)
  - Introductory remarks at a dinner honoring Lord Quinton, NYU, 17 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 22)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring George McGovern, NYU, 23 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 23)
  - "The Importance of Education: A Personal Perspective," Dutch Treat Club Lunch (NY), 23 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 24)
  - Introduction of Abraham Gitlow, Founders Day, NYU, 25 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 25)
  - Remarks delivered at the Northeast Conference on the Teaching of Foreign Languages, NYU, 26 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 26)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the Graduate School of Business Administration Conference on the Economics of Art, NYU, 26 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 27)
  - Briefing for NY delegation (Washington D.C.), 30 April 1985 (Box 618, Folder 28)
  - Bronfman Scholars Lunch, NYU, 7 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 29)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the School of Law Alumni Association's 97th Annual Dinner, NYU, 7 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 30)
  - Introduction of Abraham Gitlow at the School of Commerce Alumni Dinner, NYU, 8 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 31)
  - George Miller birthday remarks (Washington, D.C.), 8 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 32)
  - Remarks delivered at a breakfast symposium on learning disabilities, NYU, 8 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 33)
  - Statement on Dr. Brademas' role in crafting the Older Americans Act, on its 20th anniversary (Washington, D.C.), 8 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 34)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Claire Flom, NYU, 9 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 35)
  - Remarks delivered before the University Senate, NYU, 5 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 36)
  - Remarks delivered before Congregation B'nai Jeshurun (NJ), 10 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 37)
  - Rider College Education Day (NJ), 10 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 38)
  - Introductory remarks delivered at the School of Medicine Alumni Day, NYU, 11 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 39)
  - Essay exploring Dr. Brademas' role in the evolution of the Older Americans Act, 16 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 41)
  - President's Message, Students' Guide to NYU, 20 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 42)
  - Brief remarks at an event at the Grey Art Gallery, filmed by CBS, 20 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 43)
  - Remarks delivered at Industry Day, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, NYU, 20 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 44)
  - Remarks at a luncheon announcing a grant from the Carnegie Corporation to establish a Center for Study of War, Peace & the News Media at NYU, 23 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 45)
  - Remarks at a dinner in honor of the Grey Art Gallery, NYU, 23 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 46)
  - Commencement address, Wagner College (Staten Island), 26 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 47)
  - Medical Library Association Annual Meeting, NYU, 27 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 48)
  - Alumni Federation Dinner, NYU, 29 May 1985 (Box 618, Folder 49)
  - Michael Schimmel High Tea, NYU, 3 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 50)
  - Introduction of honorary degree recipients, Board of Trustees Dinner, NYU, 5 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 51)
  - Washington Square and University College Baccalaureate Ceremony, NYU, 5 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 52)
  - School of Medicine Commencement, NYU, 6 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 53)
  - Remarks delivered at the 153rd Commencement, NYU, 6 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 54)
  - School of Dentistry commencement, NYU, 7 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 55)
  - Spanish Institute Seminar, NYU, 14-15 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 56)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception and dinner in honor of Edward E. Barr, NYU, 26 June 1985 (Box 618, Folder 57)
  - Notre Dame Essay on Education (IN), 1 July 1985 (Box 618, Folder 58)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the International Federation of Library Associations & Institutions (Chicago, IL), 19 August 1985 (Box 618, Folder 59)
  - "Higher Education in the Year 2000," interview in Ladies Home Journal, 7 August 1985 (Box 618, Folder 60)
  - "Politics & Education Reform", article for National Forum, 28 August 1985 (Box 618, Folder 61)
  - Brief remarks at a reception for class agents from the School of Law, NYU, 4 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 62)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, 12 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 64)
  - American Council for the Arts National Conference, NYU, 22 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 65)
  - "Spain in the 1980s: The Domestic Transition & A Changing International Role," Woodrow Wilson Center Conference (Washington, D.C.), 25-26 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 67)
  - School of Continuing Education/Head Start 20th Anniversary, NYU, 26 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 68)
  - Stanley Fink Dinner, NYU, 26 September 1985 (Box 618, Folder 69)
  - Kriser/Weiner Dinner, NYU, 1 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 70)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, NYU, 1 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 71)
  - Visit by Frank Hodsoll, NYU, 1 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 72)
  - Remarks by Jay Oliva at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 10 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 73)
  - Mayor's Proclamation: Tisch School of the Arts Day, NYU, 15 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 74)
  - Convocation for Prime Minister Peres of Israel, NYU, 21 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 76)
  - 50th Anniversary of Courant Institute for Mathematical Studies, NYU, 22 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 77)
  - Stephen & Beatrice Brademas Lecture, 24 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 78)
  - Convocation for Alfred Gottschalk, NYU, 28 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 79)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on the Handicapped of the Committee on Labor & Human Resources, on PL 94-142 (Washington, D.C.), 29 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 80)
  - Remarks on tax reform and its effects on higher education, Higher Education Capital Finance Symposium (NY), 31 October 1985 (Box 618, Folder 81)
  - Central Opera Service National Conference, New York, undated (Box 618, Folder 82)
  - The Rita & Stanley H. Kaplan Center Dinner Dance (NY), 6 November 1985 (Box 618, Folder 83)
  - The Ernest J. & Elena A. Bruno Memorial Lecture (NY), 7 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254667
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, 7 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 2)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education and Labor, on the 20th Anniversary of the Higher Education Act (San Marcos, TX), undated (Box 619, Folder 3)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a dinner honoring the School of Business and Public Administration, NYU, 11 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 4)
  - Brief remarks delivered on the School of Dentistry Fall Alumni Day, NYU, 15 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of the Dr. Louis Blatterfein Center for Preclinical Sciences at the NYU Dental Center, 18 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 6)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the Real Estate Institute Breakfast, NYU, 18 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 7)
  - Yale Club Speech (NY), 19 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 8)
  - Remarks regarding international education at American universities delivered on the occasion of Dr. Brademas' induction into the Academy of Athens, 26 November 1985 (Box 619, Folder 9)
  - Don Forman Mini-Gym Dedication, NYU, 3 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum on graduate education issues relating to the reauthorization of the Higher Education Act, 4 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 11)
  - Mainstream/Church & Society International Recognition Banquet (NYC), 10 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Conference on Not-For-Profit Sector, NYU, 11 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, 12 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Campaign Lunch, NYU, 17 December 1985 (Box 619, Folder 15)
  - Briefing for Ted Fiske interview, NYU, 6 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 16)
  - Helen Frankenthaler Presentation (NYC), 6 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 17)
  - Starr Foundation/Nussenzweig Press Conference, NYU, 7 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 18)
  - Highlights of the Presidency at New York University, 10 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 19)
  - Symposium on Budget Balance (NYC), 10 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 20)
  - Friends of Nancy Hanks (NYC), 13 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 21)
  - School of Continuing Education Paul McGhee Medal Lecture & Dinner, NYU, 13 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 22)
  - Welcome remarks at a dinner honoring Dean Ed Kaufman, NYU, 16 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico Residence Center Commencement (San Juan, PR), 18 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 24)
  - Introduction of Edward Muskie, lecturer before the Center for National Policy, NYU, 30 January 1986 (Box 619, Folder 26)
  - General talking points for remarks delivered in Palm Beach, 1 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 27)
  - First All-University Florida Alumni Day Brunch (Hollywood, FL), 2 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 28)
  - Corrigan Dinner, NYU, 5 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 29)
  - Draft press release on FY 87 budget, NYU, 7 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 30)
  - Dinner for Margaret Atwood (NYC), 12 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 32)
  - Draft position paper on education (Wilson), 13 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 33)
  - Urban Research Center Press Conference, NYU, 24 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 34)
  - Metro Center Benefit Lunch, NYU, 25 February 1986 (Box 619, Folder 35)
  - NYU Magazine essay, 1 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 36)
  - "Building Toward the 21st Century: The Challenges of Higher Education," NYU Annual Report, 1 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 37)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, 2 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 38)
  - Great Artists Series honoring Louise Nevelson (NYC), 5 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 40)
  - International Relations Study Center, NYU, 5 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 41)
  - Welcome remarks at the National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony, NYU, 6 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 42)
  - Introduction of President Gerald Ford at a School of Business and Public Administration Conference, NYU, 7 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 43)
  - International Celebration '86 Lecture, NYU, 10 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 44)
  - Welcome remarks at the Presidential, University & Education Scholars Breakfast, NYU, 11 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 45)
  - Briefing for the NY Delegation (Washington, D.C.), 12 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 46)
  - New York University Senate, NYU, 13 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 47)
  - Association for Children & Adults with Learning Disabilities International Conference (NYC), 13 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 48)
  - Brief remarks at the 33rd Annual Graduate School of Business Administration Business Conference, NYU, 15 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 49)
  - 16th Annual Real Estate Insititute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYC), 19 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 51)
  - Welcome remarks for the Visiting USIA Educators Group, NYU, 24 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 52)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial Rally, NYU, 25 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 53)
  - Welcome remarks, the Third Olive Branch Awards Ceremony (NY), 25 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 54)
  - Remarks delivered at a Tisch School of the Arts Press Luncheon honoring Yuri Lyubimov and Zelda Fichandler, NYU, 26 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 55)
  - Mayor's Press Conference on the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions, NYU, 26 March 1986 (Box 619, Folder 56)
  - Welcome remarks at a screening of Spain: Ten Years After…, NYU, 2 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 58)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered on a trip to Florence, Italy, 3 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 59)
  - Presentation of the C. Walter Nichols Award to Felix Rohatyn, NYU, 3 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 60)
  - Touro College Convocation (Huntington, NY), 13 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 61)
  - Lunch for Westchester Guidance Counselors, NYU, 14 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 62)
  - Constatine Trypanis Dinner, NYU, 15 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 63)
  - Remarks delivered at a University Senate Meeting, NYU, 17 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 64)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, NYU, 17 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 65)
  - All-University Alumni Branch meeting, (Washington, D.C.), 18 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 66)
  - "Scholarship & Public Policy," delivered at a Library of Congress Symposium (Washington, D.C.), 18 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 67)
  - Remarks delivered at the Graduate School of Public Administration Dean's Day, 19 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 68)
  - Luncheon for Roger Penrose, NYU, 23 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 69)
  - A Nation at Risk Conference (Salt Lake City, UT), 26 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 70)
  - "The Values of Higher Education," Davie Forum Public Lecture (San Francisco, CA), 28 April 1986 (Box 619, Folder 71)
  - "Between the Summits," Alerdinck East-West Media Conference IV, 703 Main Building, 2 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 72)
  - NYU-Alerdinck Conference/Lunch, NYU, 2 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 73)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, 5 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 74)
  - Notre Dame Alumni Club of NY Dinner (NYC), 6 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 75)
  - Welcome remarks for the National Commission on Excellence in Educational Administration New York Seminar, NYU, May 8, 1986 (Box 619, Folder 76)
  - Remarks delivered before the University Senate, NYU, 8 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 77)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the annual School of Commerce/School of Business and Public Administration Dinner, NYU, 8 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 78)
  - Henry R. Ferrettie Memorial Dinner (Mishawakie, IN), 10 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 79)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures of the Committee on Ways & Means (Washington, D.C.), 12 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 81)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a Spanish Civil War Symposium, NYU, 14 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 82)
  - Annual Heights Colleges Awards Dinner, NYU, 16 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 83)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dedication, NYU, 19 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 84)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication, NYU, 21 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 85)
  - Annual Dinner Meeting for the New York Alliance for the Public Schools, NYU, 27 May 1986 (Box 619, Folder 86)
  - Trustees Dinner celebrating honorary degree recipients, NYU, 4 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 87)
  - Introduction of Tip O'Neill at NYU Commencement, 5 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 88)
  - School of Medicine Commencement, NYU, 5 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 89)
  - Introduction of Governor Dukakis (NYC), 6 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 90)
  - Welcome remarks for the School of Continuing Education Summer Writers Conference, NYU, 10 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 91)
  - Forum on State Economic Development Policy, NYU, 17 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 92)
  - Welcome remarks at a reception for the University Athletic Association, NYU, 23 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 93)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Conference for Health Managers, NYU, 30 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 94)
  - Art News interview (NYC), 30 June 1986 (Box 619, Folder 95)
  - Commentary for Social Education (NYC), 2 July 1986 (Box 619, Folder 96)
  - Liberty Weekend Conference (NYC), 6 July 1986 (Box 619, Folder 97)
  - Welcome remarks at a dinner honoring Chinese presidents, NYU, 10 July 1986 (Box 619, Folder 98)
  - Essay on education in 2011 A.D. (NYC), 22 July 1986 (Box 619, Folder 99)
  - Salzberg Seminar (Salzburg, Austria), 12 August 1986 (Box 619, Folder 100)
  - Harvard Symposium on Liberal Learning (Cambridge, MA), 3 September 1986 (Box 619, Folder 101)